python-dotenv==1.0.1        # For reading environment variables stored in .env file
langchain==0.2.2
langchain-community==0.2.3

# GROK: Replace OpenAI Embeddings with Grok-compatible LLM or custom embeddings
# NOTE: Grok currently lacks a public SDK like OpenAI. Integration might require custom API wrappers.
# If using a local LLM or Grok-compatible wrapper, include it here:

# Example placeholder for Grok or local LLM client
# grok-client==0.1.0  # (If a package becomes available)
# OR use `transformers`, `llama-cpp-python`, etc. depending on setup

unstructured==0.14.4        # Document loading
chromadb==0.5.0             # Vector storage

# Removed:
# openai==1.31.1             # ❌ Specific to OpenAI
# tiktoken==0.7.0            # ❌ Tokenizer for OpenAI models

# Optional: Alternative tokenizer if Grok provides one
# grok-tokenizer==0.1.0
